<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jakub Pelc</title>
    <link>https://swpelc.eu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jakub Pelc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://swpelc.eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://swpelc.eu/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://swpelc.eu/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact You can find me on:&#xA;GitHub LinkedIn Instagram Or you can write me an email.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://swpelc.eu/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://swpelc.eu/cv/</guid>
      <description>Jakub Pelc Illecillewaet Glacier, Canada, 2023 Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree student of Open Informatics at FEE CTU in Prague. [ swpelc.eu ] . [ contact@swpelc.eu ] . [ LinkedIn ] . [ GitHub ] . [ Instagram ] I&amp;rsquo;m interested in machine learning, drones, web development, astronomy, travelling, photography, and self improvement.&#xA;Education Gymnázium Benešov (2014 - 2022)&#xA;Bachelor (2022 - ongoing)&#xA;Open Informatics (FEE CTU, Prague, Czech Republic) Experience Lecturer at Technologická gramotnost (2022-present)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://swpelc.eu/energoplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://swpelc.eu/energoplay/</guid>
      <description>Energoplay In the year 2021 as a part of team of 3, we created a project called Energoplay, an interactive game focused en energetics and sustainability.&#xA;This project won the 1st place in the national finals of Energetická olympiáda.&#xA;We then worked for about a year (during our spare time) on the project with the help of Energetická gramotnost, ČEPS and FEE CTU, and released it publicly in the following year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://swpelc.eu/if24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://swpelc.eu/if24/</guid>
      <description>InstallFest 2024 I have presented my project QtRvSim Web Evaluation at InstallFest 2024 in Prague, Czech Republic. A conference for Linux and open-source enthusiasts.&#xA;The slides of this talk can be viewed here (English). The talk is also recorded on YouTube (Czech). An article about it can also be found on root.cz.&#xA;The conference has also been attended by Mitch Altman, the co-founder of Noisebridge hackerspace, and the inventor of TV-B-Gone, whose talk has been very inspiring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://swpelc.eu/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://swpelc.eu/profile/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Jakub Pelc I&amp;rsquo;m a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree student of Open Informatics at FEE CTU in Prague.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m interested in:&#xA;machine learning drones web development astronomy travelling photography NixOS❄ and much more.&#xA;I also part time work as a lecturer at Technologická gramotnost and Škoda Auto.&#xA;I help with organizing Astronomická expedice.&#xA;See my CV or the list of links below if you are interested. Thank you!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://swpelc.eu/web_eval/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://swpelc.eu/web_eval/</guid>
      <description>QtRVSim web evaluation This is a web evaluation system for student RISC-V submissions in course b35apo. Users can submit their RISC-V (in some cases C) code, and it will be evaluated using QtRvSim (will be checked for correct output), and the runtime will be measured (in cycles).&#xA;The app is written in Python using Flask framework, the database system is PostgreSQL.&#xA;The main aim of the app is to provide a simple and easy way to implement a task (create a new task), and to be modular in a way (so it is possible to extend this system by writing another evaluator module for another language).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
